flaberry.com 2013-05-22

# Privacy Policy

* * *

Your privacy is important to flaberry. In Order to safeguard your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our privacy practices and the choices you can make about the ways in which information about you is collected and used at www.flaberry.com. We encourage you to read and review the terms of this Privacy Policy before using our Web site.

**Information We Collect**

**Personally Identifiable Information**

To fulfill your requests for information, enable you to participate in our offerings, and provide you with opportunities to learn about other products and services in which we think you might be interested, we ask that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

In some instances, we may request that you submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments pages or in any forum and blogs that we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control any content generated on such pages and request you to use your discretion while doing so.

**How We Use the Information**

We use your personally identifiable information to provide the requested information or content, respond to your inquiries about our offerings, offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, or for other purposes disclosed at the time of collection. We also may use your personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of our products or services, or regarding changes to our Privacy Policy, or other policies or terms that affect you and your use of our Web site or our products and services. In addition, we may use such information to improve the content and navigation of our Web site, or for other internal purposes.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or information. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.

We may combine the information we collect with information available from other sources, including information received from promotional partners or other third parties. 

Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Information Sharing**

We at flaberry are committed to protecting your information and is not disseminated at any time to any other third party.

**Cookies & Web Beacons**

To enhance your experience with our site, many of our Web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the website that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. Most browsers allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer. However, please be aware that some features of our Web site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. We do not control cookies that you may occasionally get from third-party sites.

"Web beacons" or clear .gifs are small pieces of code placed on a Web page to monitor the behavior of and collect data about the visitors viewing a Web page. For example, Web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a Web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use Web beacons on this site from time to time for these and other purposes.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us and whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to, maintain security of, and correctly use the information we collect. Personally identifiable information and account activity are also protected through the use of e-mail addresses and passwords. In order to maintain the security of your information, you should protect the confidentiality of such information used to log into your account. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information.

**How You Can Access and Update Information**

If you have previously provided any personally identifiable information to us by way of our Web site, you retain the right to review, correct, update, delete or otherwise modify such information.

To access the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you that we maintain, or to correct factual errors in such information, simply log into your account using your e-mail address and password to update your information. You may also choose to write us below on info@floshowers,com. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Privacy Policy for Minors**

We do not knowingly collect information from minors. If you are under the age of 18, we request that you do not provide any personally identifiable information to us.

**How to Contact Us:**

You can contact us at [support@floshowers.com](mailto:info@floshowers.com) (or visit Contact section of our site).
